Act 1: Workspace Orchestration
Creating isolated project workspaces
Switching between workspaces instantly
No tab clutter — each workspace is its own context
Act 2: Terminal Power
Spinning up named terminals with commands
Running commands, reading output — all programmatically
Claude Code has full terminal access
Focus switching between terminals
AI agents orchestrate real dev workflows
Act 3: Terminal I/O & Special Keys
Interactive control — keystrokes, wait-for-text, read-grid
Act 4: Quick Claude — Parallel AI Agents
Spawning multiple Claude Code instances instantly
Each agent gets its own git worktree
Isolated branches, zero conflicts
Act 5: Cross-Terminal Orchestration
Moving terminals between workspaces
Act 6: Git Worktree Integration
Native worktree support for parallel development
Act 7: Session Persistence
Terminals survive app restarts — tmux-level persistence
Act 8: Phone Remote Control
Approve AI actions from your pocket
Login, browse sessions, tap quick actions
Real-time SSE notifications on your phone
Act 9: Full Orchestra
Multiple workspaces, parallel agents, phone control
5 Claude Code instances across 3 workspaces
Monitor and approve from your phone
Act 10: Cleanup
Closing demo terminals and workspaces